BANDI BHARATHKUMAR

About Myself

Being the Customer Service related fields with over 2.5 years of full experience and 4.5 years of part time experience including sales, office support, and customer care. Familiar with major customer service, conflict resolution, and possess a Positive attitude ,Problem Solving, Flexibility, Purpose Perisistence Resilience, Courge and Creating. Aiming to use my proven skills to effectively fill the managerial role in your company.

EDUCATION DETAILS

B.COM (Computers) with 61% KAKATIYA UNIVERSITY 2015-2018

M.E.C (Intermediate) with 65% KAKATIYA UNIVERSITY 2012-2015

SSC with 9.2 GPA From WISDOM HIGH SCHOOL 2011-2012

Content



9059 284 295



gautamnanda1996@gmail.com



RoomNo-11 Block-1, RGV Phase-II Laxmiguda, Katedan, Hyderabad-500005

SKILLS

Microsoft Office Suite

Excel, Word Document

Excellent Communication Skills

30 WPM Typing

Financial Documentation And Reporting

Planning and Coordination

Team Player

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2019 - Present

AIRPORT OPERATIONS AND CUSTOMER SERVICE (AOCS) as EXECUTIVE /INDIGO AIRLINES/RGIA AIRPORT

- Handling passengers and Performing the duties of the Ground Staff and I will be a
 Supervisor who leads the Team for flights departure, ensuring the safety and security of
 the flight from the arrival and till the departure of the flight.
- Handling 7+ Arrival and Departure flights passengers with more than 100+ passengers from
 each flight daily, with duties including safety, security, OTT(On Time Target), OTP(On time
 Performance) and maintaining the In-time in releasing the baggage with the support team.
- Doing Security Checks of entire aircraft after Arrival and Pre departure from sabotage.
- Training the new joined staff and making familiar with ramp, operations and SOP at the station to ensure to be ready to face any challenge at operations on RAMP.
- Maintaining the Flight Documents(ARC, AER Books and Registers) Day to Day.
- As a Executive we deal with the pilferage in the Cargo or the from the Passenger baggage by the Handling Agencies.

2014-2019

ACCOUNTS OFFICER & OFFICE ASSISTANT (Part Time) / KAPIL TOWERS/WARANGAL

- As a Incharge of the office Observing the staff work and Maintaining the office and verifying the
 office cash and cheque transactions, dealing the the customers facing the payment delays and
 irregular payments and satisfying them with work done.
- Verifying the bank payments from and to the customers and tallying the BRS.
- Remained courteous and calm, even during moments of customer dissatisfaction and trying 100% hard to satisfying the customers.